[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 9, "question": "Kyung what do we know about exactly what happened today?", "question_tokens": ["Kyung", "what", "do", "we", "know", "about", "exactly", "what", "happened", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "RB", "WP", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 10, "answer": "Well, what passengers are telling us is that they - it was just a normal day at the airport when suddenly, they heard very, very loud popping.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "passengers", "are", "telling", "us", "is", "that", "they", "-", "it", "was", "just", "a", "normal", "day", "at", "the", "airport", "when", "suddenly", ",", "they", "heard", "very", ",", "very", "loud", "popping", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 20, "question": "Is that the correct position?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "correct", "position", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 21, "answer": "That is absolutely correct.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "is", "absolutely", "correct", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["Los Angeles", "Pennsville"]}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "RB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "VBZ", "WP", "VBG", "RP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "What else have we learned?", "question_tokens": ["What", "else", "have", "we", "learned", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "Yeah, Piers, we're starting to get a better picture him, if not his recent life out in Los Angeles and certainly is what growing up here on the east coast in his background here with his family standing outside of his dad's home near in Pennsville, the police have been here for most of the night now.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "Piers", ",", "we", "'re", "starting", "to", "get", "a", "better", "picture", "him", ",", "if", "not", "his", "recent", "life", "out", "in", "Los", "Angeles", "and", "certainly", "is", "what", "growing", "up", "here", "on", "the", "east", "coast", "in", "his", "background", "here", "with", "his", "family", "standing", "outside", "of", "his", "dad", "'s", "home", "near", "in", "Pennsville", ",", "the", "police", "have", "been", "here", "for", "most", "of", "the", "night", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "CC", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "Did you have any indication from people you talked to?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "have", "any", "indication", "from", "people", "you", "talked", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "I don't know, the only indication I have was from a gentlemen I wrote in the bus with through the holding area who said he saw the shooter from down that hallway and it was a large rifle, it had a scope and this gentlemen that I talked to believe that there was a red dot from that scope that moved across his chest, and the chest of the people around him, other than that one account, your guess or you're reporting and certainly is as good as mine.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", ",", "the", "only", "indication", "I", "have", "was", "from", "a", "gentlemen", "I", "wrote", "in", "the", "bus", "with", "through", "the", "holding", "area", "who", "said", "he", "saw", "the", "shooter", "from", "down", "that", "hallway", "and", "it", "was", "a", "large", "rifle", ",", "it", "had", "a", "scope", "and", "this", "gentlemen", "that", "I", "talked", "to", "believe", "that", "there", "was", "a", "red", "dot", "from", "that", "scope", "that", "moved", "across", "his", "chest", ",", "and", "the", "chest", "of", "the", "people", "around", "him", ",", "other", "than", "that", "one", "account", ",", "your", "guess", "or", "you", "'re", "reporting", "and", "certainly", "is", "as", "good", "as", "mine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Philadelphia"]}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "When this started you heard these bullets going off and this guy shooting indiscriminately, what was going through your head?", "question_tokens": ["When", "this", "started", "you", "heard", "these", "bullets", "going", "off", "and", "this", "guy", "shooting", "indiscriminately", ",", "what", "was", "going", "through", "your", "head", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "Well, I was going to board on flight to Philadelphia.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "going", "to", "board", "on", "flight", "to", "Philadelphia", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", ":", "NN", "POS", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "I mean how do you feel finally about what happened today?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "how", "do", "you", "feel", "finally", "about", "what", "happened", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "I feel extremely grateful and I feel angry that this feels like Ground Hog Day and, you know, there's -- everyone's always saying it's too soon to have a discussion about Assault Rifles, well I just went through trauma and I think that right now is not too soon.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "feel", "extremely", "grateful", "and", "I", "feel", "angry", "that", "this", "feels", "like", "Ground", "Hog", "Day", "and", ",", "you", "know", ",", "there", "'s", "--", "everyone", "'s", "always", "saying", "it", "'s", "too", "soon", "to", "have", "a", "discussion", "about", "Assault", "Rifles", ",", "well", "I", "just", "went", "through", "trauma", "and", "I", "think", "that", "right", "now", "is", "not", "too", "soon", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "RP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "WP", "RB", "VBD", "NNS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "And is there anything that can be done in light of what's happened to improve security at places like LAX?", "question_tokens": ["And", "is", "there", "anything", "that", "can", "be", "done", "in", "light", "of", "what", "'s", "happened", "to", "improve", "security", "at", "places", "like", "LAX", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "Well Piers, as somebody who was in public service for 35 years, our hearts and prayers go out to the loved ones of those who lost loved ones today.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "Piers", ",", "as", "somebody", "who", "was", "in", "public", "service", "for", "35", "years", ",", "our", "hearts", "and", "prayers", "go", "out", "to", "the", "loved", "ones", "of", "those", "who", "lost", "loved", "ones", "today", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "What was your reaction to that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "reaction", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "Well Piers let me just say, that's a silly idea.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "Piers", "let", "me", "just", "say", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "silly", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "Some of the last few weeks, has it been as I said a comedian's dream?", "question_tokens": ["Some", "of", "the", "last", "few", "weeks", ",", "has", "it", "been", "as", "I", "said", "a", "comedian", "'s", "dream", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "They say that about everything.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "say", "that", "about", "everything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "I mean, you've covered this for so long, what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "you", "'ve", "covered", "this", "for", "so", "long", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "RB", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "Well I think the country in general is on a decline.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "I", "think", "the", "country", "in", "general", "is", "on", "a", "decline", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "I mean should somebody carry the can for the fact that the system has started so badly?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "should", "somebody", "carry", "the", "can", "for", "the", "fact", "that", "the", "system", "has", "started", "so", "badly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "MD", "VB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "You know, I'm not a big fan of scapegoating.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "a", "big", "fan", "of", "scapegoating", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "Ever?", "question_tokens": ["Ever", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "Well no, well yeah ever if it's actually scapegoating.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "no", ",", "well", "yeah", "ever", "if", "it", "'s", "actually", "scapegoating", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 231, "question": "Who knows all the details, why get rid of her now to make the situation worse?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "knows", "all", "the", "details", ",", "why", "get", "rid", "of", "her", "now", "to", "make", "the", "situation", "worse", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "When she says we're going to bring you the A Team.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "she", "says", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "bring", "you", "the", "A", "Team", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "Where was the A Team before?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "was", "the", "A", "Team", "before", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "Well that's absolutely true, there's no defense for that I would never defend him on that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "that", "'s", "absolutely", "true", ",", "there", "'s", "no", "defense", "for", "that", "I", "would", "never", "defend", "him", "on", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "Is it really credible what that the President, who's massive legacy may be based around this, didn't know anything about it being problematic?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "really", "credible", "what", "that", "the", "President", ",", "who", "'s", "massive", "legacy", "may", "be", "based", "around", "this", ",", "did", "n't", "know", "anything", "about", "it", "being", "problematic", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "WP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "Not credible and not excusable.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "credible", "and", "not", "excusable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "This is grand dad not knowing how to use the Internet right?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "grand", "dad", "not", "knowing", "how", "to", "use", "the", "Internet", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "Exactly, you know, well if I use the clicker will I get another, you know.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", ",", "you", "know", ",", "well", "if", "I", "use", "the", "clicker", "will", "I", "get", "another", ",", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "That's the patriotic thing to do about a program that is trying to bring healthcare to people in this country who don't' have it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "the", "patriotic", "thing", "to", "do", "about", "a", "program", "that", "is", "trying", "to", "bring", "healthcare", "to", "people", "in", "this", "country", "who", "do", "n't", "'", "have", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "''", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "Now I've warmed you nicely to the top of the pot and the boiling center was coming out of you.", "answer_tokens": ["Now", "I", "'ve", "warmed", "you", "nicely", "to", "the", "top", "of", "the", "pot", "and", "the", "boiling", "center", "was", "coming", "out", "of", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "JJ", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNPS", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "Well you might (inaudible), what do you make of her arguments?", "question_tokens": ["Well", "you", "might", "(", "inaudible", ")", ",", "what", "do", "you", "make", "of", "her", "arguments", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "Oh it's always -- perfect, perfectly wrong, you know, right it's the Democrats who only care about power that's right.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "it", "'s", "always", "--", "perfect", ",", "perfectly", "wrong", ",", "you", "know", ",", "right", "it", "'s", "the", "Democrats", "who", "only", "care", "about", "power", "that", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "Could it be him against Chris Christie?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "it", "be", "him", "against", "Chris", "Christie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "It probably will be.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "probably", "will", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Christie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ted Cruz"]}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "And who will prevail?", "question_tokens": ["And", "who", "will", "prevail", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "You know, if it's the primary voters who vote every time, I think it will be Ted Cruz.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "if", "it", "'s", "the", "primary", "voters", "who", "vote", "every", "time", ",", "I", "think", "it", "will", "be", "Ted", "Cruz", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "Well yeah, what it would mean for America and for America's reputation do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Well", "yeah", ",", "what", "it", "would", "mean", "for", "America", "and", "for", "America", "'s", "reputation", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "You know, we don't know until he became President what it would mean.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "we", "do", "n't", "know", "until", "he", "became", "President", "what", "it", "would", "mean", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "What does this say about American culture that those two issues, people are very happy to move with times and change but one is culturally, apparently irrevocable?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "this", "say", "about", "American", "culture", "that", "those", "two", "issues", ",", "people", "are", "very", "happy", "to", "move", "with", "times", "and", "change", "but", "one", "is", "culturally", ",", "apparently", "irrevocable", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "CD", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "CC", "CD", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "Well because first of all we're the gun (ph) in the country.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "because", "first", "of", "all", "we", "'re", "the", "gun", "(", "ph", ")", "in", "the", "country", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "Will it ever change?", "question_tokens": ["Will", "it", "ever", "change", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "Probably not in my lifetime.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "not", "in", "my", "lifetime", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "Are you surprised at the speed with which both those things have moved in public opinion?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "surprised", "at", "the", "speed", "with", "which", "both", "those", "things", "have", "moved", "in", "public", "opinion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "No I would hardly call it speedy.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "I", "would", "hardly", "call", "it", "speedy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "WP", "NNS", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "WP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "Could you see a time in 30, 40 years in America where issues like gay marriage, marijuana became Federal issues or just a Federal Law encompassing the whole of America?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "see", "a", "time", "in", "30", ",", "40", "years", "in", "America", "where", "issues", "like", "gay", "marriage", ",", "marijuana", "became", "Federal", "issues", "or", "just", "a", "Federal", "Law", "encompassing", "the", "whole", "of", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", ",", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "WRB", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNS", "VBD", "NNP", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "Absolutely, I mean that's what happens when a tipping point is reached with the states, I think that's what will happen with gay marriage and probably some day with marijuana itself.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", ",", "I", "mean", "that", "'s", "what", "happens", "when", "a", "tipping", "point", "is", "reached", "with", "the", "states", ",", "I", "think", "that", "'s", "what", "will", "happen", "with", "gay", "marriage", "and", "probably", "some", "day", "with", "marijuana", "itself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 400, "question": "Well I thought it moved quite quickly you don't think it has?", "question_tokens": ["Well", "I", "thought", "it", "moved", "quite", "quickly", "you", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "has", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 401, "answer": "No I don't think it has, it's because people always found it so easy to get weed.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "has", ",", "it", "'s", "because", "people", "always", "found", "it", "so", "easy", "to", "get", "weed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "You're asking me to choose between my children?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "asking", "me", "to", "choose", "between", "my", "children", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Carlin"]}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "Will you literally you do stand up till the day they carry you out in the box?", "question_tokens": ["Will", "you", "literally", "you", "do", "stand", "up", "till", "the", "day", "they", "carry", "you", "out", "in", "the", "box", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "RP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "George Carlin did.", "answer_tokens": ["George", "Carlin", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "Would that be your dream exit from life?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "that", "be", "your", "dream", "exit", "from", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "It would be a great way to go.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "would", "be", "a", "great", "way", "to", "go", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ray Kurzweil"]}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "DO you think you'll live to be a 100?", "question_tokens": ["DO", "you", "think", "you", "'ll", "live", "to", "be", "a", "100", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "AHER: Well I'm hoping Ray Kurzweil is correct and I'll live forever.", "answer_tokens": ["AHER", ":", "Well", "I", "'m", "hoping", "Ray", "Kurzweil", "is", "correct", "and", "I", "'ll", "live", "forever", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "IN", "VBG", ",", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "Right but does it matter?", "question_tokens": ["Right", "but", "does", "it", "matter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "Well it does matter because when we didn't use to have these kind of places where you could retreat to your, you know, ghettoization of thinking, public discourse was the better for it because you had to hear a conflicting idea and now you don't.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "it", "does", "matter", "because", "when", "we", "did", "n't", "use", "to", "have", "these", "kind", "of", "places", "where", "you", "could", "retreat", "to", "your", ",", "you", "know", ",", "ghettoization", "of", "thinking", ",", "public", "discourse", "was", "the", "better", "for", "it", "because", "you", "had", "to", "hear", "a", "conflicting", "idea", "and", "now", "you", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "Wrestling?", "question_tokens": ["Wrestling", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "If that doesn't get what I'm saying nothing will.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "that", "does", "n't", "get", "what", "I", "'m", "saying", "nothing", "will", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "You couldn't even remember that happening?", "question_tokens": ["You", "could", "n't", "even", "remember", "that", "happening", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "I was watching the other day, it's really not even coming back to me.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "watching", "the", "other", "day", ",", "it", "'s", "really", "not", "even", "coming", "back", "to", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jay Leno", "Jay Leno"]}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "What do you make Jay Leno?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "Jay", "Leno", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "I love Jay Leno, I'm on a bash with Jay Leno.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "Jay", "Leno", ",", "I", "'m", "on", "a", "bash", "with", "Jay", "Leno", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jay Leno"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "Why does he get such a hard wrath from other comedians, is it a jealousy?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "does", "he", "get", "such", "a", "hard", "wrath", "from", "other", "comedians", ",", "is", "it", "a", "jealousy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PDT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "Well of course a lot of it is that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "of", "course", "a", "lot", "of", "it", "is", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "Because what I understand I mean incredibly nice, charming?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "what", "I", "understand", "I", "mean", "incredibly", "nice", ",", "charming", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jay"]}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "``", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 518, "question": "He does it himself right?", "question_tokens": ["He", "does", "it", "himself", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "He doesn't have someone talking in the ear of the network executive like the other guys do saying, \"Get rid if Jay, he's too old.\"", "answer_tokens": ["He", "does", "n't", "have", "someone", "talking", "in", "the", "ear", "of", "the", "network", "executive", "like", "the", "other", "guys", "do", "saying", ",", "``", "Get", "rid", "if", "Jay", ",", "he", "'s", "too", "old", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "Do you have an agent?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "an", "agent", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "Of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]